Mehera Basu

Full stack developer

Kolkata, West Bengal

https://github.com/octogenex

https://stackoverflow.com/cv/octogenex

https://www.linkedin.com/in/octogenex

Summary of qualifications

I look forward to work with an organization which offers a challenging

opportunity to enhance my

knowledge, skills and experience that would allow me to contribute towards

achieving the

organizational goals to the best of my potential.

Special Full Stack Web Development, Python Development, Deep Learning,

Artificial Intelligence.

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer

Creamson Intelli Private Limited

Duration: August 2019 to Present

My daily responsibility includes writing API in Python Flask, designing Python

Jinja templates and extracting data from PDF using Python Regex, Designing

front end in Angular 7, Writing database query in MySQL, sometimes looking

Linux server and troubleshooting Linux and windows systems

Angular Developer

Creamson Intelli Private Limited

Duration: April 2019 to Present

Angular Developer Intern

Creamson Intelli Private Limited

Kharagpur, West Bengal

Duration: October 2018 to March 2019

Worked on 3 projects with my mentor, 1 project with my colleague and 1 with my self

Education

B.Tech in computer science

MAKAUT

Skills

- PYTHON (Less than 1 year)
- BOOTSTRAP (Less than 1 year)
- CSS (Less than 1 year)
- HTML5 (Less than 1 year)
- JAVASCRIPT (Less than 1 year)

Additional Information

Technical Qualification

Python, Machine Learning, Angular, Angular Material, Typescript, Javascript, HTML5, CSS, BOOTSTRAP